Driving north on 81, the autumn leaves are
golden red My family is all around me, trying to
clear my head We're headed for the parkway, just
a perfect normal day Then we hit the sign at
Lexington, the gauntlet's underway The ghost
is in the car again, the ghost is in the lane Two
blue shields side by side, her voice is in my
brain I-64 the eastbound sign and 81 the north, I
know the exits follow
This is the 30 mile gauntlet I'm holding on so
tight I'm trying to be normal I'm trying to win
the fight But every sign is like a cut A reminder
of a trap I'm just a passenger Caught in the ring,
green map
We're getting close to Stanton now The split is
coming fast Exit 221, a test I have to pass Mark
just asked me, are you ready? I look him in the eye
I have to face this demon I'm ready, I will try
We're on the ramp, the turn is made It's time for
Richmond East The world just stops, the light
just fades The monster is unleashed It's her
road, it's her prison It's the place I cannot be
Get me off, get me off She's coming, she's got me
System crash I64
That is not my name System crash She's at the door
She's won the game I can't breathe, I can't see
Get me out, get me free No, no, no, no
Exit 91